{
    "subject": "resource/John_F._Kennedy",
    "predicate": "property/religion",
    "object": "resource/Catholic_Church",
    "human_readable": "John F. Kennedy's religion is the Catholic Church.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9146355986595154,
            "question": "Was John F. Kennedy Catholic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8190253376960754,
            "question": "John F. Kennedy's religious affiliation was?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8108600378036499,
            "question": "What is John F. Kennedy's religion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7303423285484314,
            "question": "John F. Kennedy identified as a member of which religious organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6460931301116943,
            "question": "What is the name of the religion practiced by John F. Kennedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309928894042969,
            "question": "To which religious institution did John F. Kennedy belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6222179532051086,
            "question": "Which church did John F. Kennedy belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4207756221294403,
            "question": "What was John F. Kennedy's belief system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4035603106021881,
            "question": "What faith did John F. Kennedy practice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3857782185077667,
            "question": "Which denomination did John F. Kennedy follow?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John F. Kennedy's religion is the Catholic Church.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6870_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What faith did John F. Kennedy practice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6870_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was John F. Kennedy's belief system?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6870_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which church did John F. Kennedy belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6870_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6870_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several references to John F. Kennedy's Catholic faith, including his speech addressing Protestant ministers and discussions about him being the first Catholic president in the United States. This supports the statement that John F. Kennedy's religion is the Catholic Church."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}